Cuz he said he made the beat in 5
minutes, I actually believe him.
>> I'm a [__] walking paradox. No, I'm
not.
>> So, the main quote unquote sample comes
from a It's an FX pack, so it's just
like random weird sounds. So, I pulled a
couple of the sounds that would be on if
you were just pressing keys on this
sample pack, you would find stuff like
this.
Just Just ran
Just random [__] like this, and then one
of them just happens to be
that.
So, all he does is just eighth notes.
That one sound.
If you listen to the sound closely, when
it starts, that's not the peak of the
sound. It kind of rolls into the sound,
so the peak is offbeat. So, listen.
Like it rawr, kind of ramps up quick
like that. And so, when you repeat it,
you get that natural like slump. That
natural slump when you put a straight
beat to it,
that's where the magic is. It's that
I mean, it's automatically syncopated
and just like so groovy. There's no
hi-hat, either.
It's so simple. And so, when he comes
in, his voice is just so crystal clear.
>> Swallow this cinnamon. I'mma scribble
this [__] and [__] while she is telling
me that she's been getting intimate with
men.
>> For me, it's aged very well. It feels
like a cultural artifact. Put her in a
museum. This represents a time, you
know.
>> Yeah.